MUHAMMAD SALEEM



ABOUT US

As a graphic designer, I'm obsessed with the art of visual communication. I believe that effective design has the power to inspire, educate, and persuade. My expertise lies in Logo design and branding, Print and digital design, UI/UX design, Typography and visual storytelling

CONTACT



soleplexs@gmail.com



+92 309 237 6233



in/saleem-saeed

LANGUAGES

English



Urdu



EDUCATION

INTERMEDIATE

From Karachi (2024)

MATRICULATION

From Karachi (2020)

EXPERIENCE

UMBRELLA HEATH CARE SYSTEMS (LLC)

Graphic Designer In karachi (2023 - Now)

GETGOAL SOLUTIONS

Graphic Designer In Karachi (2021 to 2023)

INSTAZAP

JUNIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER In Karachi (2020 to 2021)

GETGOAL SOLUTIONS

JUNIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER In Karachi (2016 to 2021)

SKILLS

Illustrator
Photoshop
Figma
After Effect
Premiere Pro
Blender
Html